아, 정말 좋네요!
Oh, that feels so good.
난 운도 좋아!
커피에 라이브 섹스 쇼까지!
Oh, lucky me.
Coffee and a live sex show.
- 뭐라구요?
- 네?
- I'm sorry, what?
- I'm sorry.
아무것도 아녜요
엠마한테 책 읽어주고 있었어요
- Nothing. I was just reading to Emma.
- From Cosmo?
코스모폴리탄?
네, 그래요
Yeah. Yeah, it's:
'아름다운 피부를 위한
나만의 비법'이죠
"Climax Your Way to Better Skin."
오늘 쇼핑해야 하는데
난 쇼핑 싫어해요
So I have to go shopping today,
which is my least favorite thing.
옷은 정말 못 고르겠어요
I'm so bad at picking out clothes.
그럼 패션에 대해 잘아는
사람이 도와주면 좋겠네요
So you need someone who knows
fashion to tell you what looks good.
난 제발 빼줘, 제발..
Not me. Not me. Not me.
- 맞다! 레이첼?
- 응?
- Oh, hey, Rach?
- Yeah?
- 찰리랑 같이 쇼핑 갈수 있어?
- 글쎄..
- Maybe you could take Charlie shopping?
- Oh, well..
- 더 좋은 약속이 있겠죠
- 레이첼은
- I'm sure you have better things to do.
- You kidding?
쇼핑광인 걸요?
패션감각도 아주 뛰어나요
Rachel loves to shop,
and she has great taste.
나도 레이첼한테 많이 배웠어요
'노동절 지나면 하얀 옷 입지 말아라'
She's the one that taught me not
to wear white after Labor Day..
'옷 입어볼땐
반드시 속옷을 입어라'
and to always, always, always put
on underwear when trying on clothes.
시간 있으면 좀 도와줄래요?
그러면 정말 고맙겠어요
If you have the time,
I'd really appreciate the help.
그래요, 그렇게 하죠
Okay. Yeah, let's shop.
아주 멋지고 우아한 옷을
고를수 있을 거예요
Okay, you are gonna come back
with some very classy clothes.
야한 속옷도 사라! 꼭!
And some slutty lingerie. Slutty!
네, 좋아요!
안녕!
Okay, great. All right, bye.
내가 못살아!
Pain in the ass!
- 꺼진거 맞지?
- 무슨 일인데?
- That's off, right?
- What's the matter, Phoebe?
마이크의 누나가 오늘 저녁
파티에 초대했는데 마이크도 온대
Mike's sister just invited me to
a party tonight and he's gonna be there.
"걱정 말아요, 마이크는 피비가
오는거 아무렇지도 않대요"
She was like, "Don't worry. I asked him
and he's totally okay with seeing you."
그러니까 나도 가서 아무렇지
않다는걸 보여줘야해
So now I have to go so he'll think
that I'm totally okay with seeing him.
하지만 넌 아니잖아
마이크 때문에
- Which you're not. You're hung up on him.
- Exactly.
- 많이 힘들어했구
- 맞아!
그럼 마이크가 속상하도록
근사하게 차리고 가야겠구나
You want him to eat his heart out,
so you have to look fabulous.
그건 생각도 못했네!
I didn't even think about that.
정치적인 남녀관계
정말 지긋지긋해!
Sexual politics!
찰리와 쇼핑 갈건데
Phoebe, I'm taking Charlie shopping.
- 너도 가자, 내가 도와줄게
- 그거 좋겠다!
- Come and I'll help you find something.
- That'd be great.
좋겠다! 여자셋이 야한
속옷 걸쳐보겠네!
Oh, isn't that nice? The three of you,
trying on slutty lingerie together.
우린 그럴생각 없는데?
- That's not what we're gonna do.
- Why'd you ruin it? Who was I hurting?
왜 초치고 그래?
해끼치는 것도 없구만!
프렌즈 시즌 9
'완벽한 정자의 조건!'
'여성의 생식 기관'
Fortunately, she has
a very pretty face.
와! 이 여자 다행히
얼굴은 미인이네
아직도 믿어지지가 않아
I still can't believe this. My uterus
is an inhospitable environment?
내 자궁이 '거주에 부적당한
적대적인 환경'이라구?
난 좋은 집주인이 되려고
항상 노력해왔단 말야!
I've always tried so hard
to be a good hostess.
내 정자가 운동성이
낮다는 것도 못 믿겠어!
I can't believe my sperm
have low motility.
나 사춘기 때는 놈들 성격이
정말 엄청 급했다구!
While I was growing up, they sure
seemed to be in a hurry to get places.
- 잘 있었어요?
- 안녕하세요
- Hi there.
- Hi.
지난주 검사결과에서
새로운 소식은 없습니다
I'm sorry there wasn't better news
from your tests last week..
두분에게 가능한 방법들을
알려드리죠
but I wanted to talk to you
about your options.
좋아요
Okay.
두분이 자연적인 방법으로
임신할 가능성은 적지만
Even though your chances of conceiving
through natural means aren't great..
혹시 모르니까 기본적으로
성관계는 계속하세요
you never know,
so keep having sex on a regular basis.
이런 젠장!
Oh, damn it!
시간이 지나면 이사람
유머에 적응하실수 있을 거예요
Don't worry.
After a while, you'll tune it out.
두분의 상황으로 볼때
성공 가능성이 높은 방법은
Given your situation, the options
with the greatest chances for success..
대리모와 정자를 제공받아
인공수정 하는 방법입니다
would be surrogacy
or insemination using a sperm donor.
둘다 내키지 않으시면
입양도 하실수 있습니다
If you feel that neither of those is
right for you, you could always adopt.
그거 일종의 암시인가요?
Is that a hint?
박사님을 좋아하긴 하지만
우리집에 입양할 생각은 없어요
Because we love you, Dr. Connelly,
but we don't want you to be our child.
와, '적대적인 환경'이
바로 이런 거군
Wow! Talk about
an inhospitable environment.
안녕, 피비 만나서 쇼핑 갈건데
준비됐어요?
Hi. Okay, you ready to go pick up
Phoebe and go shopping?
- 어서 가요!
- 쇼핑 잘해요
- Let's do it.
- All right, have a good time.
그안에는 옷이 없을텐데..
Not gonna find any clothes in there.
- 안녕
- Hey, you guys.
- Hi.
국제 고생물학회 주제 발표자로
누가 물망에 올랐게요?
Guess who's up for keynote speaker
at the National Paleontology Conference?
- 크리스 베일리?
- 그사람이
- Chris Bailey?
- Yeah, right.
초안제출 마감일
지킨게 언제였죠?
When was the last time he made
a submission deadline for an abstract?
넌 왜웃어?
Why are you laughing?
고생물학자가 된 기분이
어떤지 궁금해서
Just seeing what it'd be like
to be a paleontologist.
재미있다!
It's fun. Yeah.
- 로스가 후보에 올랐어요?
- 네
So you're up for keynote speaker?
- 누가 결정하는데요?
- 셔먼 교수님
- Who's deciding?
- Professor Sherman.
- 오늘 뵙기로 했어요
- 여간해서 설득하기 힘든 분인데..
- I'm meeting with him today.
- He's a pretty tough guy to impress.
그분을 압도할수 있는
비장의 무기가 있죠
I think I know how to dazzle him.
설마 마술 하려는건 아니지?
You're not gonna to do
a magic trick, are you?
아냐!
No.
- 안녕
- 잠깐, 너희들한테 물어볼게 있어
- Hey, guys.
- I want to ask you something.
이번 고생물학회에서
내가 연설하게 되면
I may get to speak
at this paleontology convention.
너희들도 와서
들어주면 정말 좋겠다
If I do, I'd love for you guys
to come and hear me.
우리 모두 집안일이 있거나
일 때문에 바쁘거나 아플거야
I think I can safely say that we all have
family issues, work and/or are sick.
- 바베이도스에서 하는데?
- 하지만 네가 우선이지
- It's in Barbados.
- But you come first.
나 갈게
I'm there.
- 글쎄, 난 몸이 좀..
- 바베이도스는 카라브해에 있어
- I don't know Ross, I'm not feeling too..
- Barbados is in the Caribbean, Joe.
왜 진작 말 안했어?
Why didn't anybody say so?
- 나중에 봐요
- 안녕
- See you later.
- Okay, bye.
- 안녕
- 잘가
- Bye. See you.
- Bye.
- 불임클리닉에서는 어땠어?
- 저번처럼 재미있지는 않았어
- So how did it go at the fertility clinic?
- Not as much fun as last time.
정액을 내놔야만 포르노를 보여줘
Apparently, you only get porn
if you're giving a sperm sample.
그래서 의사가 뭐래?
So, what did the doctor say?
대리모를 쓰는 방법이 있는데
There's surrogacy, but Monica's dreamt
her whole life of carrying a child..
모니카의 평생 꿈이
아기를 갖는 거였기 때문에
대리모를 지켜보는건
모니카가 견디기 힘들거야
and she just felt that watching
a surrogate would be too hard for her.
- 그럼 대리모는 제외야?
- 그래
- So you're ruling out surrogacy?
- Yeah.
그럼 그게 뭔지
공부 안해도 되는거지?
So I don't have to learn
what that means?
입양외에 남은 방법은
인공수정 뿐이야
Aside from adoption, the only
other choice is insemination..
그래서 정자제공자에 대해
생각중이야
so we're talking about sperm donors.
됐어, 내가 해줄게
모니카 어디있어? 위에?
Enough said. I'm there for you, man.
Where is she, upstairs?
네가 정자를
제공해준다니 고맙다만
Your long-standing offer to have sex
with my wife is appreciated.
- 사양이다
- 네 기분은 어때?
- But I think I'll pass.
- So how do you feel about all this?
아기를 갖는데 더 쉬운 방법이 있으면
좋겠지만 다른수가 없는것 같아
I wish there was an easier way for us
to have a child, but there isn't one.
로스! 네가 선심 써라
큰맘 먹고 용기를 내
Come on, Ross, be a good guy.
Step up and do it.
뭘?
What?
뭐?! 안돼!
벤을 줄순 없어!
What?! No!
I'm not gonna give them Ben!
이 화석의 DNA와 MRI검사 결과는
The data we're receiving
from MRI scans and DNA testing..
정말 놀랍습니다
of these fossils are staggering.
우리는 지금까지 리키의
연대를 기정사실로 받아들였죠
I mean, we've been accepting
Leakey's dates as a given.
하지만 10만년이나 차이가 난다면
But if they're off
by even a 100,000 years or so..
기존의 가설은 모두
쓰레기통으로
then you can just throw
most of our assumptions..
들어가야 합니다!
you know, right in the trash.
그러니까 제말은..
So, what I'm saying is..
그게..
Is that..
엄청난 반향이
일어나게 된다는 거죠
Is that repercussions could be huge.
고생물학뿐만 아니라
I mean, not just in paleontology,
but if you think about it..
진화생물학, 유전학
지질학까지도 말입니다
in evolutionary biology,
genetics, geology.
정말 큰 사건이 될거예요
I mean, truly, the mind boggles.
별로 관심이 없으시군요
Well, that's not what you want.
- 남성 향수 인센티브예요
- 좀 뿌려줘요
- Incentive for Men?
- I'll take some of that.
- 저건 남자향수야
- 이따
- Phoebe, that's for men.
- I know.
파티에서 마이크 만날텐데
When I go to the party later..
다른 남자 냄새 풍겨서
내가 괜찮다는걸 보여줄 거야
Mike will know I'm over him
because I'll smell like another guy.
고마워요
Okay.
오, 이런! 내 애인은
러시아 택시운전사야
Oh, good, I'm dating
a Russian cabdriver.
이거사는 사람이 있어요?
꼭 무 냄새 같잖아요!
Seriously, does anyone buy this?
I smell like beets.
난 어깨에 패드가 들어간
재킷이 마음에 들어요
I really like those jackets with the
shoulder pads in them. Where are those?
내가 입으면 어떨것 같아요?
워킹걸에 나오는
멜라니 그리피스 같을 거예요
On Melanie Griffith in Working Girl.
여기 괜찮은게 있을것 같아요
I think what you want is over here.
이래서 난 누가
도와줘야 한다니까요
See, I told you I needed someone.
감사인사도 할겸 레이첼한테
뭔가 해주고 싶어요
By the way, as a thank you,
I would really love to take you out.
- 정말요?
- 조이와 오늘 영화보기로 했는데
- Really?
- Joey and I are going to a movie tonight.
- 같이 갈래요?
- 안돼요
- You want to come?
- Oh, I can't.
이미 봤거든요
Because I've seen them.
영화를 전부 다 봤어요?
You've seen all the movies?
네, 난 광이거든요
Yeah. I'm a big fan.
영화광이죠
Of the movies.
활동사진 말이에요
You know, motion pictures.
발성영화
The talkies.
나랑 탈의실에 같이 갈래?
Rach, will you come with me
to a dressing room?
- 그래
- 가자
- Sure.
- Okay.
그럼 다른 계획을 세워보죠
Maybe we could do something else.
같이 할만한게 있을지 모르겠어요
난 안해본게 없거든요
You know, that depends on what it is.
I've done a lot of stuff.
너 왜 그러는 거야?
찰리가 싫어?
So, what were you doing out there?
Do you not like Charlie?
아니, 괜찮아
그냥 느낌이 별로 안좋아서 그래
She's okay. I don't know, I just don't
get a really good vibe from her.
- 왜?
- 몰라
- Why?
- I don't know.
똑똑한 머리로
여기저기 휘젓고 다니고..
You know, just the way
she waltzed in here all smart..
키도 크고..
and tall, you know..
조이 혼을 쏙 빼놓으니까
다른 사람은 기회가 없잖아!
and just swept Joey off his feet.
Nobody else has a chance.
- 다른 사람 누구?
- 누구든지 간에!
- Who else?
- Anybody.
너, 나..
You. Me.
모니카 어머니..
You know, Monica's mom.
너 조이 좋아하니?
You like Joey?!
쉿! 피비!
Phoebe!
그래, 조이한테 약간
감정이 있는건 사실이야
All right, look, I do.
I have a little thing for him. Just..
- 맙소사!
- 그냥 육체적인 거야
- Oh, my God.
- It's just physical.
혼자 이러다 말거니까 걱정마
둘이 같이 있는걸 보면
I have it totally under control, okay?
It's just when I see them together..
질투가 좀 나서 그래
sometimes, I just get a little jealous.
와! 얄궂다, 전엔 조이가
널 좋아하더니 지금은..
Wow. Isn't that ironic
that he liked you, and now you like..?
나도 알아!
I get it!
혼자 그러다 말 정도라면
All right, as long
as it's under control.
너 아무짓도 하면안돼
조이는 이미 찰리와 사귀고 있다구
You can't do anything about it.
He's already dating her.
그리고 찰리는 좋은 사람이야
그건 옳지 않다구
She is a nice person.
That wouldn't be right.
그래, 나도 알아
정말 별일아냐
I know, I know.
So it's just not a big deal.
- 이건 우리만 아는거다
- 그럼 물론이지
- So can we keep this between us?
- Sure.
그래, 빨리 나가야겠어
그 무 냄새 향수 너무 독하다
Great, because I gotta get out of here.
The smell of beets is killing me.
찰리한테 귀머거리
쌍둥이가 있으면 좋으련만
Any chance Charlie has a deaf twin?
안녕
- Hi, honey.
- Hey.
내 친구야, 저녁같이
먹자고 초대했어
I brought a friend home for dinner.
This is Zack from work.
회사동료 잭이야
다시 만나서 반가워요, 잭
Oh, of course. It's so nice
to see you again, Zack.
- 저두요
- 처음보는 사이면서
- You too.
- You guys haven't actually met before.
둘다 예의가 바르네
But, boy, you're both polite.
앉아, 잭
맥주 갖다줄게
Have a seat. I'll get you a beer.
내가 가져올게
- I got it.
- Thanks.
- 괜찮은 친구 같지?
- 그런것 같아
- So Zack's pretty nice, huh?
- Yeah, I guess.
자기랑 저 친구 반반씩
닮은 아기 낳는거 어때?
So how would you like to have a baby
that's half yours and half his?
뭐라구?
Excuse me?
우리 정자 제공자 찾고 있잖아
잭도 후보가 될수 있어
We're talking about sperm donors,
and Zack may be the guy.
똑똑하고 건강하고 운동도 아주 잘해
환상적인 정자라니까!
Look. He's intelligent, he's healthy,
he's athletic. I mean, he's sperm-tastic!
자기 미쳤어?!
도대체 뭐라고 한거야?
Chandler, this is crazy.
Well, what did you even say to him?
"우리 마누라 만나보고
자네 정자좀 주게" 그랬어?
"Come up. Meet my wife.
Give us your sperm."
자기더러 잭을 직접 만나보라고
저녁에 초대한 거야
I invited him to dinner so you'd get
a chance to get to know him.
정자은행을 통하면 사람을
만나거나 알아볼 기회가 없잖아
With a sperm bank, you never
meet the guy, get to check him out.
- 챈들러!
- 진짜 멋진 친구라니까
- Chandler!
- I'm telling you, he's great.
내 정자에 문제가 없었대도
저친구 탐났을 거라구!
I mean, even if my sperm worked fine,
I think he'd be the way to go.
난 동의할수 없어
I'm not going to be a part of this.
아무나 집에 데려와서 정자
제공자가 되어 달라곤 할수없어!
You can't bring some random guy home
and expect him to be our sperm donor.
알았어
Okay.
- 잭?
- 고마워
- Zack?
- Thanks.
컵 받침 있어?
물자국 남기긴 싫거든
Do you have a coaster?
I don't want to make a ring.
자기 얘기좀 해봐요, 잭
Tell me about yourself, Zack.
어떡해! 들었을까?
들었다면 정말 곤란한데!
Oh, God, do you think she heard?
It'd be so bad if she heard.
못 들었을지도 몰라
내가 저기 들어가서 말해볼 테니까
Maybe she didn't hear. I'll go into that
dressing room and talk. You stay here.
- 들리는지 확인해봐
- 알았어
- See if you can hear me.
- Okay, great.
다행이다!
네말 한마디도 안들려
Oh, thank God,
I can't hear a word that you're saying.
- 아직 아무말도 안했어
- 다시 들어가서 말해봐
- I didn't say anything yet.
- Well, get back in there and talk.
난 레이첼이야
I'm Rachel.
친구들한테 전화해서 우리 엠마
바꿔주는거 참 짜증나는 일이야
It's so annoying when I put Emma
on the phone to talk with my friends.
뭐야?!
What?
차마 네 면전에 대고
못하는 얘기를 한거야
Well, some things are just hard
to say to your face.
좋아, 어쨌든 다 들었어
그럼 찰리도 들었다는 뜻이 돼
Okay, well, I heard that.
Which means that she heard it too.
- 큰일났다!
- 어떡할 거야?
- We have a problem.
- Oh, what are we gonna do?
솔직하게 얘기해요
Just be honest with her.
내가 미쳐!
Oh, my God!
그리고 사람들이 자기 아기
전화 바꿔주는거 정말 짜증나요
It is annoying when parents
put babies on the phone.
됐어요! 참견 말아요!
All right, enough out of you!
고마워요
Thank you.
뭐가 잘못된 거야?
이건 훌륭하단 말야
Where did I go wrong? This is good stuff.
여보세요?
- Hello?
- I need to talk to Charlie. Is she there?
조이, 찰리랑 통화해야 하는데
옆에 있니?
아니, 레이첼이랑 쇼핑 갔어
왜? 무슨 일인데?
No, she went shopping with Rachel.
Why? What's up?
주제발표 하는 문제로
셔먼 교수님을 만나고 있거든
I'm meeting with Professor Sherman
about my being the keynote speaker.
- 아! 어떻게 됐어?
- 아주 잘되고 있어
- How's it going?
- It could be better.
교수님이 잠드셨어
He fell asleep.
뭐? 난 벌써 버뮤다 행 표
샀단 말야!
What? But I already bought
my ticket to Bermuda!
- 바베이도스야!
- 알았어, 그럼 차 빌려서 타고 갈게
- Barbados.
- Fine, I'll rent a car and drive.
넌 그일 꼭 따내야해!
You have to get that job.
어떡하면 좋지?
완전히 골아 떨어졌어
What am I supposed to do?
He's out cold.
사실 아까 잠꼬대를
잠깐 하셨는데
In fact, he was just talking
in his sleep before..
프랜이라는 사람한테 엉덩이를
세게 때려달라고 하더라
and evidently he wants someone
named Fran to "spank him harder."
- 그냥 깨워
- 안돼
- Well, just wake him up.
- I can't.
내 얘기를 듣다가 잠든걸 알면
나 주제발표 안시킬 거야
If he realizes that I'm the one who
put him to sleep, I won't get the job.
그것 참 곤란하군
That's a tough one.
아, 잠깐만!
나도 전에 그런적이 있어!
Oh, wait a minute.
This happened to me before.
연극 오디션 중이었는데
제작자가 잠들었거든
Yeah, I was auditioning for a play,
and the producer fell asleep. I..
아니다!
No, wait a minute.
잠든 사람은 나였어
It was me who fell asleep.
셰익스피어 말야, 가끔 추격신
좀 넣으면 어디 덧 나냐?
I mean, hey, Shakespeare, how about
a chase scene once in a while?
- 저녁준비 다됐어요
- 손 씻고 올께
- Hey, guys, dinner's ready.
- I'm gonna go wash up first.
고마워
Thanks.
어때? 우리 애한테 저 친구
유전자를 넣었으면 좋겠어
What do you think? I want his genes
for my kid. Those eyes, those cheekbones.
저친구 눈이며, 광대뼈며..
자기 지금 꼭 게이 같은거 알아?
Okay, there's enthusiastic,
and there's just plain gay.
- 잭이 마음에 안드는구나?
- 좋은사람 같아
- You don't like him.
- I think he's fine.
하지만 실제 어떤
사람인지는 모르잖아
But we don't know
anything real about him.
- 더 많은 정보가 필요해
- 알았어, 내가 하는 대로만 따라와
- I wish we could get more information.
- All right, just follow my lead.
- 집이 아주 좋은데요?
- 고마워, 나도 우리집이 '미치게' 좋아
- You guys have a great place here.
- Thanks. I'm crazy about our place.
말이 나와서 말인데
Hey, speaking of crazy..
가족 중에
정신병력 있는 분이 있나?
do you have a history
of mental illness in the family?
아니, 듀카키스한테
투표한 삼촌이 한분 계시긴 하지
No. Although, I did have an uncle
who voted for Dukakis.
우리가 말하는건
그런게 아냐, 잭!
That's really not the kind of thing
we're looking for.
알았어
Okay.
두사람 어떻게 만났어요?
So tell me, how'd you guys meet?
친구였다가 런던에서 술김에..
뻔한 스토리예요
Oh, friends first, drunk in London,
you know the story.
제가 더 재미있는 질문할게요
I've got a better question for you:
가족중에 당뇨병에
걸린분이 있나요?
Do you or any of your blood relatives
have diabetes?
아뇨
No.
심장병은요? 알츠하이머는?
통풍은요?
Heart disease? Alzheimer's? Gout?
두사람 저녁 식사에
손님 초대해 본적 별로 없죠?
You guys don't have people
for dinner a lot, huh?
그냥 얘깃거리를 찾는 거예요
We're just making conversation.
알겠습니다, 오늘 정말
웃기는 얘기를 들었어
Yeah, well, okay.
I heard a joke today. It's pretty funny.
정말 안웃기는게 뭔지 알아?
남자들의 대머리 경향이야
You know what's not funny?
Male pattern baldness.
나에 대해 많은 관심을
보여줘서 몸둘 바를 모르겠어요
You guys have shown a lot of interest
in me tonight, and I'm flattered..
솔직히 좀 소름끼치는군요
and quite frankly, a little frightened.
다른 얘기좀 하면 안될까요?
Can we just talk about something else?
- 좋아요
- 그러지
- Sure.
- All right.
라비올리 정말 맛있는데요?
This ravioli's delicious.
라비올리 먹는걸 보니까
자네 치아가 아주 예술인걸?
I notice you're enjoying that ravioli
with a beautiful set of teeth.
어렸을때 교정했어?
Did you have braces as a child?
- 아니?
- 좋았어!
- No, I didn't.
- Yes!
우린 치아에 집착하는 편이거든
We're teeth people, Zack.
좋아, 부딪쳐볼래
가서 들었는지 물어볼 거야
Let's just do it. Let's just go
over there and see if she heard.
- 잘 생각했어
- 그래
- Good plan.
- Okay.
- 피비, 어디가는 거야?
- 미안하지만
- What? Where are you going?
- Oh, I'm sorry, Rachel.
네 유치한 놀이에
낭비할 시간 없어
I don't have time
for your childish games, okay?
마이크한테 아무렇지도 않다는걸
I still have to find something
incredible to wear..
보여줄 멋진옷을 골라야한다구!
so I can beat Mike
at "Who's More Over Who"!
- 어디 있었어요?
- 옷 입어봤어요
- Where have you been?
- Trying on clothes.
정말? 탈의실에서요?
이상하네!
Oh, really? In the dressing room?
Well, that's so weird.
피비랑 나도 탈의실에 있었어요!
정말 세상 좁네요!
Phoebe and I were in the dressing room.
Gosh, it's just such a small world.
레이첼?
두사람 얘기 들었어요
Rachel, I heard you
two guys whispering.
맙소사! 들었군요!
내가 설명할게요
Oh, God, you did, you heard.
Okay, look, let me explain.
설명할것 없어요
다 들었으니까
There's nothing to explain.
I heard you.
피비가 조이를 좋아하죠?
Phoebe likes Joey.
네
Yeah.
이해가 안돼요
조이를 좋아하면서
I don't understand it.
I mean, Phoebe likes Joey..
다른 남자한테 멋지게 보이려고
쇼핑을 오다뇨?
and then she's here to buy a dress
to impress another guy?
네, 피비가 원래 그런 애예요
한 남자론 성에 안차거든요
Yeah, that's Phoebe. That's Phoebe.
You know, she just wants them all.
뭐랄까, 엄청 밝혀요!
It's, like, she's nympho.
- 어머나!
- 정말이에요
- Wow!
- Yeah.
레이첼이 피비한테 가만히
있으라고 말하는거 들었어요
You know, by the way, I heard you
tell her not to do anything.
내편 들어줘서 고마워요
레이첼은 정말 좋은 사람이에요
Thanks for sticking up for me.
God, you are such a nice person.
그러려고 노력해요
I try.
오! 세상에! 저더러 주제발표를
하라구요? 진심이세요?
Oh, my God, you really want me
to be the keynote speaker?
고맙습니다!
Thank you!
천만에요
You're welcome.
우와! 먹는걸..
Wow! You look..
까먹을 정도로 멋있다!
stop-eating hot!
그건 제일 높은 등급이야!
Which is like the highest level
of hotness.
정말? 나 오늘 파티 가는거
걱정돼 죽겠거든
Okay, are you sure? Because I am
really dreading going to this party.
그럼 가지마
Then don't go.
마이크는 내가 오는걸 알아!
안가면 자기 때문인줄 알거야!
Mike knows I'm coming. If I don't show up,
he'll think it's because of him..
그럼 내 체면이 뭐가 돼?
나한텐 아주 심각한 문제라구
and then I'm gonna lose face.
That's a very serious thing in my culture.
그럼 파티에 가서 마이크는
완전히 잊은 것처럼 행동해!
All right, then you go to that party,
and you pretend to be over Mike.
그런 다음 우리집에 와
기분좋게 한잔 쏠게
Afterward, you come to my place
and I'll get you good and drunk.
그래, 좋아!
You got it. Okay.
하지만 네가 만든 와인은 사절이다
But not on the wine
that you made, okay?
또 응급실에 실려가긴 싫거든
Because I just don't want to go back
to the emergency room.
미안해요
현금이 좀 모자란데..
I'm sorry,
I don't seem to have enough cash.
혹시 루블화는 안받으시나요?
You would accept rubles, would you?
이게 백만 루블이거든요
그러니까 가치는..
This is a hundred-thousand-ruble note,
which is worth approximately..
전혀없죠
nothing.
- 데이빗?
- 피비? 잘 있었어요?
- David?
- Phoebe! Hi.
세상에!
- Oh, my God!
- Hi.
와! 정말 근사하군요!
Wow! You look unbelievable.
아, 네
Oh, yeah, well..
여긴 웬일이에요?
What are you doing here?
민스크에서 돌아왔어요
아주 온거예요
Well, I'm back from Minsk.
Permanently.
어떻게 된거예요?
Well, what happened?
내가 '원자내 소립자의'
Remember how I was trying
to achieve..
'포지트로늄 증류'를
연구해온것 알죠?
the positronic distillation
of subatomic particles?
네
Yeah.
8년간의 연구결과
Well, after eight years of research,
I discovered..
볼가능하다는 결론이 나왔어요
that it can't be done.
- 안됐네요
- 괜찮아요
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
이분야에서는 흔히있는 일이죠
This kind of thing happens
all the time in science.
과학 전문 잡지에
잘못 기재된 오타를
To people who base eight years of research
on a typo in a scientific journal.
8년동안 연구하는
사람들이니까요
어쨌든
Well..
돌아와서 잘됐네요
어떻게 지내요?
great that you're back. How are you?
- 좋아요! 재미있습니다
- 다행이네요
- Good. Good. Life is good.
- Good.
만나는 사람도 있어요
Well, I'm seeing someone.
- 어머! 잘됐네요
- 네
- Good for you.
- Yeah.
그여자도 과학자예요
아주 똑똑하고 예쁘고..
She's also a scientist,
so she's very smart and pretty and..
따지고 보면 피비 덕분에
만나게 된거예요
It's actually because of you
that we're together.
지난번에 피비가 마이크란
친구와 함께 있는걸 보고
I mean, I saw what you had
with that Mike guy..
너무 부럽다고 생각했거든요
and I just said, "Boy, I want that."
- 난 마이크와 헤어졌어요
- 정말이에요?
- Mike and I broke up.
- You're kidding me.
실은 나도 만나는 사람 없어요
거짓말 한거예요
Because I'm not seeing anybody.
I just totally made that up.
- 정말이에요?
- 왜그랬는지 모르겠지만 미안해요
- Really?
- I don't know why, I'm sorry.
아마 체면 때문에 그랬나봐요
I guess I just didn't want
to lose face.
이해해요
I understand.
그럼 우리 둘다
Yeah. Okay. So then, okay..
뉴욕에 살고
만나는 사람도 없는 거예요?
So we're both living in New York,
not seeing anyone.
- 우리한테 이런날도 오네요
- 그러게요
- That's so not like us.
- Yeah, I know.
지금 모습 보면서
이런 질문하는건 바보 같지만
Well, this is probably a stupid question,
seeing that you look like that..
지금 어디가는 중이에요?
but do you have someplace
that you need to be right now?
그게..
Well..
아뇨
No.
- 그럼 한잔 할래요?
- 좋아요
- Well, do you want to get a drink?
- I'd love to.
- 갑시다!
- 네!
- Great.
- Okay.
혹시 무 냄새 안나요?
Do you smell beets?
바람부는 쪽에 서세요
All right, stay upwind of me.
저기 피비예요!
옆에 있는 사람이 마이크예요?
Hey, there's Phoebe.
Is that Mike she's with?
아뇨, 데이빗이에요
No, that's David.
남자가 또 있어요?
There's a third guy?
저건 빙산의 일각이죠
Tip of the iceberg.
그만 가야겠어
I'm gonna take off now.
나 집에 가도되지?
You're gonna let me go home,
aren't you?
조금 더 놀다가지 그래?
Sure you don't want to stay
a little longer?
아니, 집에 가야겠어
피곤해서 말야
No, I should get home.
I'm kind of tired.
일시적인거야
늘 피곤 한거야?
Are you always tired?
만성 우울증일 수도 있거든
Because that could be
a sign of clinical depression.
우리 조부모님들 돌아가신 나이
생각해내느라 지쳐서 그래
No, it's tiring to figure out the age
at which all my grandparents died.
- 내일 보자구
- 그래
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Okay.
잘가세요
Bye.
우리 '정자'를 찾은것 같아!
I think we found our sperm.
그래, 완벽한것 같아
He does seem pretty perfect.
그렇지? 정말 그렇게 생각해?
그럼 부탁해볼까?
Yeah? You think so?
Should I ask him?
아니
No.
왜? 증조할머님이 비만이어서?
Why not? Just because his
great-grandmother was obese?
어차피 자기 닮으면 비만일거야!
Our kid's gonna get that
from you anyway.
그래서가 아냐
No, that's not it.
잭한테 이것저것
캐물어 보면서 깨달았는데
It's just that when we were asking him
all those questions before..
잭이 세상에서 제일
완벽한 남자라도 의미가 없어
I just realized I don't care if he
is the most perfect guy in the world.
- 잭은 자기가 아니니까
- 물론이지! 나보다 훨씬 나아!
- He's not you.
- Yeah, he's better!
그렇지 않아
No, he's not.
자기와 함께 갖는 아기가 아니라면
다른 어느 누구도
If I can't get pregnant with you, then
I don't want to get pregnant by him..
난 싫어!
or anyone else.
- 정말? 진심이야?
- 그래, 진심이야
- Really? Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
다행이다!
나도 그러고 싶지 않거든
Thank God, because l
don't wanna do this either.
난 자기가 그걸 원한다고
생각해서 잭을 불렀던 거야
I was just doing it because I thought
that was what you wanted.
솔직히 남편은 나라구!
정자는 내가 제공해야지
I'm the husband.
I'm supposed to bring the sperm.
날 그렇게 생각해줘서 고마워
That is so sweet.
사랑해
I love you.
좋아, 그럼 이제 남은건..
So you know this leaves us with..
입양 뿐이야
Adoption.
어떨것 같아?
How do you feel about that?
괜찮을것 같아
I think I feel okay about it.
실은 아주 좋을것 같아
Actually, I think I feel
really good about it.
나도 그래
Me too.
가정이 필요한 아기를 찾아서
자기랑 함께 키우고 싶어
I wanna find a baby that needs a home,
and I wanna raise it with you.
그리고 우리만의 방식으로
엉망진창 살아보자구
And I wanna mess it up
in our own specific way.
그럼 결정한 거야?
정말 아기 입양하는 거야?
So this is it?
We're really gonna adopt?
그래
Yeah.
- 오! 우리 부모가 되는거야?!
- 우린 좋은 부모가 될거야
- Oh, my God! We're gonna be parents!
- We are gonna be great parents.
빨리되면 좋겠어!
And it could be soon.
생각해봐, 지금 이순간
저기 어딘가에서..
I mean, think about it.
Right now, somewhere out there..
우리 아기가 잉태되고
있을지도 몰라
our baby could be being conceived.
운이 좋으면..
그리고 조용히 귀기울여 보면
Wait. If we're lucky,
and we're really, really, really quiet..
콘돔 찢어지는 소리가
들릴지도 몰라
we may be able to hear
the sound of a condom breaking.
안녕, 잭
Hey, Zack.
안녕, 챈들러
Hey, Chandler.
어제 일 사과할게
I wanted to apologize for last night.
우리 부부 때문에 불편했지?
I got the feeling
we made you uncomfortable.
- 아냐
- 정말?
- No, you didn't.
- Really?
아니, 불편했어
No, you did.
우리 부부가 중요한 문제를
결정할게 있거든
My wife and I have
some boundary issues.
그래서 간혹 부적절한
질문을 하곤 하지
Sometimes we ask
inappropriate questions.
잘 해결될것 같아
We're working on it.
- 금요일에 발표할 자료들이에요
- 고마워요
- Here are the boards for Friday's pitch.
- Thank you.
재닛은 저 아기 직접 키울거래?
혹시 알고 있어?
You wouldn't know if Jeanette's planning
on keeping her baby, would you?